<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SoulEase</string>


    <string name="Sukhasnastr">"It's the traditional meditative position of sitting on the floor with crossed legs and an upright spine. Easy position is a strong tool for recovering the strength you need to deal with anxiety, sadness, and extreme stress, despite the fact that many people don't think of it as a yoga pose. The symmetry of this posture and the base of your spine are two factors that help you overcome stress by giving you the feeling that nothing can unsettle you or push you off track."</string>
    <string name="Balasana">"Child's pose is one of the most relaxing and soothing positions in yoga. You may relax and unwind here since you're completely grounded. In times of anxiety and distress, the feeling of being supported by the soil can bring considerable mental peace. "</string>
    <string name="Andho_Mukha_Svanasana">"In Yoga, this is a very prevalent practice. It boosts blood flow to your brain while also stretching your spine and strengthening your arms, shoulders, and legs. We can get more energy and mental clarity by increasing circulation to this area, which will aid us in dealing with issues that bring us tension or anxiety."</string>
    <string name="Salamba_Sarvangasana">"Another great yoga practise for anxiety and depression relief is shoulderstand. Shoulderstand, like downward-facing dog, enhances blood flow to the brain, improving mental clarity and regulating feelings. It's necessary to highlight that you should avoid this position, if you have neck or shoulder difficulties, high blood pressure, or are menstruating."</string>
    <string name="Savasana">"This meditation posture is great for mind control, releasing stress, anxiety, and depression while also bringing clarity to your experience. This position is usually done at the end of each yoga session to allow you to absorb all of the energy and revelations you've gained throughout your exercise."</string>
    <string name="Natarajasana">"Natarajasana, also known as the Dancer Pose or Lord of the Dance Pose, is a yoga posture that requires balance and flexibility. Here are the steps to do Natarajasana:

Begin in Tadasana or Mountain Pose, standing tall with your feet together and arms at your sides.

Shift your weight onto your left foot and lift your right heel towards your buttocks. Reach back with your right hand and grasp your right ankle.

As you inhale, raise your left arm up towards the ceiling, lengthening your spine.

Exhale and slowly begin to tilt forward from your hips, extending your right leg behind you. At the same time, reach your right arm forward, away from your body.

Hold this pose for several breaths, maintaining your balance and the extension of your limbs.

To release the pose, gently lower your right leg back down to the ground and return to Tadasana.

Repeat the pose on the other side, shifting your weight onto your right foot and grasping your left ankle with your left hand.

Remember to listen to your body and only go as far as you feel comfortable. With regular practice, you can gradually increase your flexibility and balance in this pose."</string>

    <string name="Anjaneyasana">"Anjaneyasana, also known as the Low Lunge Pose, is a yoga posture that stretches the hip flexors, thighs, and groin. Here are the steps to do Anjaneyasana:

Begin in Adho Mukha Svanasana or Downward-Facing Dog Pose.

As you exhale, step your right foot forward between your hands. Place your right foot flat on the ground and align your right knee directly above your ankle.

Lower your left knee to the ground and slide your left leg back behind you. Keep the top of your left foot on the ground.

Inhale and lift your torso upright, bringing your arms up overhead.

As you exhale, sink your hips down towards the ground, feeling a stretch in your left hip flexor and right hamstring.

Hold this pose for several breaths, maintaining your balance and the extension of your arms and spine.

To release the pose, bring your hands down to the ground on either side of your right foot and step your right foot back to Adho Mukha Svanasana. Repeat the pose on the other side, stepping your left foot forward between your hands.

Remember to keep your shoulders relaxed and your gaze forward in this pose. With regular practice, you can gradually deepen the stretch in your hip flexors and thighs."</string>

    <string name="garudasana">"Garudasana, also known as the Eagle Pose, is a yoga posture that requires balance and coordination. Here are the steps to do Garudasana:

Begin in Tadasana or Mountain Pose, standing tall with your feet together and arms at your sides.

Bend your knees slightly and lift your left foot off the ground. Cross your left thigh over your right thigh, tucking your left foot behind your right calf.

As you inhale, reach your arms out to the sides and bring them up to shoulder height. Cross your right arm over your left arm, bending your elbows and bringing your palms together.

If possible, press your palms together and lift your elbows to shoulder height. If your palms do not touch, simply bring your hands as close together as you can and hold.

Hold this pose for several breaths, maintaining your balance and the intertwining of your limbs.

To release the pose, slowly lower your arms and legs back to Tadasana.

Repeat the pose on the other side, lifting your right foot off the ground and crossing your right thigh over your left thigh.

Remember to breathe deeply and maintain a steady gaze in this pose. With regular practice, you can gradually increase your balance and flexibility in Garudasana."</string>

    <string name="virabhadrasana">"Verabhadrasana, also known as the Warrior Pose, is a yoga posture that strengthens the legs and opens the hips and chest. There are three variations of Verabhadrasana, and here are the steps to do Verabhadrasana I:

Begin in Tadasana or Mountain Pose, standing tall with your feet together and arms at your sides.

Step your left foot back about 3-4 feet, keeping your right foot pointing forward and your left foot at a 45-degree angle.

As you inhale, lift your arms up overhead and bend your right knee, keeping it directly above your ankle. Sink down into your right hip, keeping your left leg straight and strong.

Square your hips and shoulders to the front of the mat, bringing your gaze forward or up towards your hands.

Hold this pose for several breaths, feeling the strength and power in your legs and core.

To release the pose, lower your arms and straighten your right leg. Step your left foot forward to meet your right foot in Tadasana.

Repeat the pose on the other side, stepping your right foot back and bending your left knee.

Remember to keep your shoulders relaxed and your gaze forward in this pose. With regular practice, you can gradually increase your strength and stability in Verabhadrasana "</string>

    <string name="AdhoMukhaVrksasana">"Adho Mukha Vrksasana, also known as the Handstand Pose or Downward-Facing Tree Pose, is an advanced yoga posture that requires strength, balance, and concentration. Here are the steps to do Adho Mukha Vrksasana:

Begin in Adho Mukha Svanasana or Downward-Facing Dog Pose, with your hands shoulder-width apart and your feet hip-width apart.

Walk your feet towards your hands, bringing your hips up towards the ceiling.

Place your hands firmly on the ground, with your fingers spread wide and your palms pressing down.

Walk your feet in closer to your hands until your hips are directly above your shoulders.

Engage your core muscles and lift one leg up towards the ceiling, keeping your hips level.

Once you feel stable on one leg, slowly lift the other leg up towards the ceiling.

Keep your gaze between your hands and maintain your balance for several breaths, using your fingertips to adjust your alignment as needed.

To release the pose, slowly lower one leg at a time back to Downward-Facing Dog Pose.

Remember to keep your shoulders strong and your core engaged in this pose. It's important to practice this pose with the guidance of an experienced yoga teacher to ensure proper alignment and safety. With regular practice, you can gradually increase your strength and balance in Adho Mukha Vrksasana."</string>

    <string name="vajrasana">"Vajrasana, also known as Thunderbolt Pose or Diamond Pose, is a simple seated yoga posture that can be practiced after meals to aid digestion. Here are the steps to do Vajrasana:

Kneel down on the ground with your knees together and your feet apart, placing your shins and the tops of your feet on the ground.

Gently lower your buttocks onto your heels, keeping your back straight and your hands on your thighs.

Adjust your feet so that your big toes are touching and your heels are slightly apart.

Rest your palms on your thighs, keeping your fingers relaxed and your gaze forward.

Take slow, deep breaths and focus on relaxing your body and mind.

Hold this pose for several minutes, allowing your breath to become slow and steady.

To release the pose, gently lift your buttocks off your heels and come back to a kneeling position.

Remember to listen to your body and avoid this pose if you have knee or ankle injuries. Vajrasana can be a helpful addition to your yoga practice as it helps to improve digestion, reduce stress, and increase blood flow to the pelvic region."</string>

</resources>
